http://www.golfmagic.com/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
Privacy Policy
Golfmagic
Crash Media is a company that is registered in the UK with Company Number 3729433 and with a registered address at Crash Media Group, 78-80 St John's Street, London, EC1M 4EH.Our Data Promise to you
Crash Media Group is absolutely committed to respecting and protecting your data whilst it is in our care. We collect your personal information because it helps us to understand your needs and guides the way in which we interact and communicate with you about our products and services now and in the future. We have strict policies and procedures in place to protect your data when you send it to us, when we process it in order to provide you with the services you have requested or, where you have given us your permission to do so, to send you information that we think you'll find interesting, and thereafter when we store your data on our secure servers.
We are notified with the Information Commissioner's Office, the regulator of the Data Protection Act 1998 and abide by its requirements.What personal data do we collect? Crash Media Group collects both Personal Data and Anonymous Data when you send us information or when you visit one of our websites. When we talk about Personal Data we mean any information that can identify you as an individual, such as your name and postal address. Anonymous Data doesn't identify you as a person but it might be used in aggregate, for instance when you participate in a survey.
How do we keep it secure? Our servers are protected using HTTP and SSL technology (where indicated), so whilst your data is in our care we know it's as secure as it can be. We are taking all reasonable steps to meet our obligations and responsibilities under the Data Protection Act 1998 and other privacy legislation, including the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).When we ask another organisation to provide a service for us, we ensure that they have appropriate security measures in place. If we or our service providers transfer any information out of the European Economic Area (EEA), it will only be transferred with the correct protection in place, as stated in UK law.
The internet is not a totally secure medium and you acknowledge and agree that Crash Media Group shall not be responsible for unauthorised use, distribution, damage or destruction of personal data, except to the extent that we are required to accept such responsibility under the Data Protection Act 1998.How do we collect and use your Personal Data? We collect your details when you register on one of our websites; subscribe to our services; subscribe to receive emails from us and our partners; participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our website, or enter a competition or promotion.
With regards to each of your visits to our websites we may automatically collect the following information:Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your device to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, unique identifiers and other device platform information;Information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products or pages you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.
Information about your interactions with our email messages, such as the links you click on and whether you open or forward a message, the date and time of these interactions and the device you use to read emails;Information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies provided by our partners and affiliatesWe will always be transparent about how we plan to use your data so that you have the choice whether or not to give it to us. We respect your preferences and will do our best to make sure that we keep our promises.
If you give us your consent to send you further marketing messages we may contact you from time-to-time with carefully selected offers and promotions from ourselves or from our network of carefully selected partners, from which you may always opt-out or unsubscribe. It is not our practice to contact you if you have made it clear that you do not wish to hear from us about our products and services.We may need to authenticate your identity to provide you with access to subscriber-only services. We might also send you surveys or invite you to enter a competition or receive a newsletter, for instance. If you do not wish to participate you may simply decline our invitations.As part of our Google Analytics tracking we have implemented the following features: Remarketing, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising by visiting here https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
We use this information for reporting purposes and to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show your ads on sites across the Internet. We may use the cookies relating to Google Analytics together with third party cookies to inform, optimise and serve ads based on a user's part visits to our websites.Do we share that data with any other companies?Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy or in the data collection statements that will always be visible when we collect your information and where we give you the opportunity to select your preferences, we may release your data to external companies that we use to process your orders, to supply you with a prize in the event you win a competition, for instance. Every supplier we use has to go through a rigorous up-front process to ensure that their processes are at least as good as our own.
However, you expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Data with those suppliers with whom we contract in order to provide services to you, otherwise we may not be able to provide the level of service that we know you'll require.If you send in a comment, we may post it on our site or use it as a testimonial without mentioning your full name or publishing any information that would identify you. Furthermore, in some circumstances we may display some of your information such as your username and age. Others may be able to see your personal data if you post any information in comments underneath articles or forums and may be used to send you unsolicited communications over which we have no control.We may share some of your information with advertisers, ad servers and ad networks to deliver targeted advertising both on our websites and on selected partner websites but this will not include any information which directly identifies you. However, by interacting with or viewing an advert, you should be aware that the third party may make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advert.
These activities may involve the use of cookies and other similar technologies. To learn more or to see how you can opt out of targeted advertising, for more information please read our Cookie Policy.Please take care when using social networking sites too which we may invite you to join that you do not disclose anything that you might later wish to retract.There are certain times when we may be legally required to disclose your data in good faith where it is required by law or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us, or where we have a requirement to protect or defend the rights of Crash Media Group or any users of our servers. We will always ensure that those requesting the information have the legal right to do so.
If another company should acquire any of our companies or our assets, including our database, that company will have the right of possession to the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations formerly attributable to us and will use the data in line with the terms under which you submitted it or as described in this Privacy Policy.The information we may collect from you about othersSometimes we may offer you the chance to invite a family member or a friend to enjoy a particular service. In such circumstances, we will collect both your personal details and those of your friend or family member. We will ask your consent to mention your name when we contact the person or persons you have recommended and we will only use this information once and not save it in our database, unless they have entered a competition, for example, when the information will be stored purely for that purpose. If they decide to take up any of our invitations then their data will be treated exactly the same as your own, using the terms under which the data was collected and the information as described in this Privacy Policy.Leaving Our website and moving on to third party websites When you click on advertisements or links on any of our sites, you will leave that site and go to a third-party site, which is outside of our control. When we place an advertisement on one of our sites, it does not signify that we are endorsing that advertiser's product or service. We do not accept responsibility for content, have no control over and our Privacy Policy does not apply to these companies, sites or content and if such third-party sites collect Personal Data, we cannot control how this data is processed, stored or used. We advise that you read their data collection statements, which accompany any registration and their Privacy Policies before you submit your personal information.Cookies and how we use them "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a website. Crash Media Group uses cookies for a number of reasons:To provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our sites.For statistical purposes to track how many users we have and how often they visit our websites.We use organisations to collect anonymous user information so they can analyse how the website is being used and the number of visitors.We and our advertisers may use statistical cookies to track who has seen an advert and clicked on it.To show you adverts that you may be interested in and to control the number of time you see them and measures the effectiveness of the ad campaign.We may use 'Flash' cookies to store your preference for your media player. If we do not use them, it may not be possible for you to watch some video content.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies, but please be aware that for some parts of our sites to work, you will need to accept cookies. For more information please visit www.allaboutcookies.org and/or www.youronlinechoices.comLogging in using social networkingIf you login to our sites using a Facebook login or a Google login, you are granting permission to Facebook and or Google login to share your user details with Crash Media Group. This will include your name, email address, date of birth and location which will then be used to form a Crash Media Group identity. This will also allow Crash Media Group and Facebook and/or Google login to share your networks, user ID and any other information you choose to share according to your Facebook and/or Google account settings.Opting Out on Receipt of Email Marketing Communications If you receive a marketing email from us, you will have the option to "opt-out" by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of each and every message we send you. Please be aware that this will not unsubscribe you from our service based messages.Telephone and Mailing Preference Services The Telephone Preference Service (TPS), the Corporate Telephone Preference Service (CTPS) and the Mailing Preference Service (MPS) allow you to choose to opt out of unsolicited marketing. However, if you are registered on any of the preference services, which are general opt-out registers, you may still receive marketing communications from us if you have given us your consent previously or if you subsequently give us that consent.Marketing to Children We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 16 for marketing purposes.International Transfer For the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, personal data may be transferred to, processed, stored and accessed by Crash Media Group and our affiliated service providers in the United States and in other jurisdictions where we or they operate. Courts and other authorities in these jurisdictions may, in certain circumstances, be entitled to access your personal data. By using our Services, you consent to this transfer, processing, storage and access of your personal data in and/or outside of the jurisdiction in which you reside. We will transfer your personal data subject to suitable safeguards, including standard contractual clauses where appropriate.Using our websites from outside the UK Some of our servers are situated in the EEA and when you submit your details, in whichever country you are situated, you agree to the data being transferred to the EEA and processed under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 which stem from European Directives 95/46/EC and 2002/58/EC respectively. If you are not in agreement please do not add your personal details on the website.How you can gain access to the personal data we collect about you Under the Data Protection Act 1998, you have the right to see what information we hold about you and you may ask us to make any changes that you consider necessary to make the information accurate. If you want to apply to see the data we hold about you, please write to:The Data Protection OfficerCrash Media Group78-80 St John's StreetLondonEC1M 4EHWe will require that you satisfactorily identify yourself to demonstrate your entitlement to view this data.Questions regarding this Privacy Policy If you have comments or questions related to this Privacy Policy please email dataprotectionofficer@crash.net and we will respond as promptly and as fully as we can.Complaints will be dealt with by the Data Protection Officer and will be responded to within 30 days. If you are not satisfied with the response you should refer your complaint to the ICO https://ico.org.uk/concerns/Changes to this Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy will be amended from time-to-time if we make any important changes in the way that we collect, store and use personal data. We may notify you by sending an email to your last known email address or writing to your last known postal address to direct you to the Privacy Policy if the changes are material. Our dispatch of a communication to you will, in any event, constitute notification.Any changes will be effective immediately.This Privacy Policy was last revised in May 2018.
Latest NewsGolf newsOCEANTEE announces as supplier to the Ladies European TourGolf newsScottish golf club saved as 135 golfers sign up to joinGolf newsUK golf club suddenly closes despite enjoying golf boom in 2020Equipment newsFIRST LOOK: Cobra RADSPEED irons in Variable and ONE Length versions for 2021Equipment newsBryson DeChambeau says he's "HITTING BOMBS" with new Cobra RADSPEED driver!
Latest ReviewsDriversCobra RADSPEED Drivers Review | The Driver To Beat In 2021!IronsCallaway Big Bertha B21 Iron Review: Best Game-Improvement Irons of 2020?GPS DevicesSamsung Galaxy Watch Golf Edition Review: The golf watch PACKED with featuresGPS DevicesGolfBuddy Laser Lite Review: the rangefinder that will save you A LOT of moneyGPS DevicesIs the Shot Scope Pro L1 the BEST value for money laser rangefinder?
Latest Tips and InstructionIron PlayStop coming over the top in your golf swing INSTANTLY with this practice drillBest tips and instructionHow to use your BODY in the golf swing and generate natural POWER!Best tips and instructionHow the CATAPULT golf swing method can completely change your gameBest tips and instructionDustin Johnson: Breaking down The Masters champion's swingBest tips and instructionMake your golf swing more natural with this SIMPLE trick
Crash Media Group Crash.net Visordown.com
Our Privacy PolicyCrash Media Group Ltd 2020.
